Hello and welcome to Fidelity Family Office Services. I've
lived and worked in Dallas for over 25 years,
and I'm delighted to be in this vibrant region.
I have experience working on the investment side within a
family office and enjoy working with single and multi family
offices as well as wealthy families. We take a
consultative approach to helping our client's solve the challenges they
face, whether it's thinking about starting a new family
office, executing an investment policy statement, meeting complex
, reporting needs or providing resource is around family matters
. I've helped create a network of single and multi
family offices, including wealthy families in the Greater Southwest
region, and connect these individuals with peers to share
best practices. As an example, I organize dinners
around the region for families interested in networking around direct
investments. In addition, I host an annual workshop
for single family office executives providing outside speakers who present
on topics of interest. We also help families through
transitions, including succession planning and structuring a new family
office. I'm happy to talk with you about how
we can help meet your unit needs. I look
forward to getting to know you and your family better